export const data = [
  {
    question: "Who was the first man created by God?",
    option1: "Abraham",
    option2: "Moses",
    option3: "Adam",
    option4: "Noah",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which book of the Bible contains the story of Jesus' birth?",
    option1: "Genesis",
    option2: "Exodus",
    option3: "Matthew",
    option4: "Revelation",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the mountain where Moses received the Ten Commandments?",
    option1: "Mount Sinai",
    option2: "Mount Zion",
    option3: "Mount Moriah",
    option4: "Mount Olive",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the prophet who was swallowed by a whale?",
    option1: "Isaiah",
    option2: "Jeremiah",
    option3: "Ezekiel",
    option4: "Jonah",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the city where Jesus was crucified?",
    option1: "Jerusalem",
    option2: "Bethlehem",
    option3: "Nazareth",
    option4: "Galilee",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the king of Israel who defeated the giant Goliath?",
    option1: "Saul",
    option2: "David",
    option3: "Solomon",
    option4: "Jonathan",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the river where Jesus was baptized?",
    option1: "Jordan",
    option2: "Nile",
    option3: "Euphrates",
    option4: "Tigris",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the apostle who denied Jesus three times?",
    option1: "Peter",
    option2: "John",
    option3: "Matthew",
    option4: "Judas",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the city where the apostles received the Holy Spirit on Pentecost?",
    option1: "Jerusalem",
    option2: "Antioch",
    option3: "Ephesus",
    option4: "Corinth",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the prophet who wrote the book of Isaiah?",
    option1: "Isaiah",
    option2: "Jeremiah",
    option3: "Ezekiel",
    option4: "Daniel",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the king of Babylon who destroyed Jerusalem?",
    option1: "Nebuchadnezzar",
    option2: "Darius",
    option3: "Cyrus",
    option4: "Xerxes",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the apostle who was bitten by a snake on the island of Malta?",
    option1: "Paul",
    option2: "Peter",
    option3: "John",
    option4: "Luke",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the mountain where Jesus gave the Sermon on the Mount?",
    option1: "Mount Sinai",
    option2: "Mount Zion",
    option3: "Mount of Olives",
    option4: "Mount of Beatitudes",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the prophet who was taken up to heaven in a whirlwind?",
    option1: "Elijah",
    option2: "Elisha",
    option3: "Isaiah",
    option4: "Jeremiah",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the city where the apostle Paul was imprisoned for two years?",
    option1: "Jerusalem",
    option2: "Caesarea",
    option3: "Rome",
    option4: "Ephesus",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the king of Israel who built the temple in Jerusalem?",
    option1: "David",
    option2: "Solomon",
    option3: "Rehoboam",
    option4: "Hezekiah",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the prophet who wrote the book of Revelation?",
    option1: "John",
    option2: "Matthew",
    option3: "Mark",
    option4: "Luke",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the city where Jesus appeared to the disciples after his resurrection?",
    option1: "Jerusalem",
    option2: "Galilee",
    option3: "Bethlehem",
    option4: "Emmaus",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the king of Israel who was known for his wisdom?",
    option1: "Saul",
    option2: "David",
    option3: "Solomon",
    option4: "Rehoboam",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the river that the Israelites crossed to enter the Promised Land?",
    option1: "Jordan",
    option2: "Nile",
    option3: "Euphrates",
    option4: "Tigris",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the apostle who was known as the 'apostle to the Gentiles'?",
    option1: "Peter",
    option2: "Paul",
    option3: "John",
    option4: "James",
    ans: 2,
  },
]
